let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "What was the name of Arya's first word ? Reference : Game of Thrones",
    answer: "Needle",
    options: [
      "Oathkeeper",
      "Needle",
      "Stormbreaker",
      "Longclaw"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What was the name of the man who eloped with Tommy's sister, Ada ? Reference : The Peaky Blinders",
    answer: "Freddie",
    options: [
      "Henry",
      "Freddie",
      "Campbell",
      "Danny"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "At what position does Harry play on his Quidditch Team ? Reference : Harry Potter",
    answer: "Seeker",
    options: [
      "Chaser",
      "Keeper",
      "Seeker",
      "Bludger"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What instrument did Ross intend to play at Monica and Chandler's wedding ? Reference : F.R.I.E.N.D.S.",
    answer: "Bagpipes",
    options: [
      "Keyboard",
      "Saxophone",
      "Flute",
      "Bagpipes"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "How many infinity stones where there ? Reference : Marvel",
    answer: "6",
    options: [
      "6",
      "4",
      "5",
      "7"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "Who out of these was a DEA Agent ? Reference : Breaking Bad",
    answer: "Hank",
    options: [
      "Skyler",
      "Tuco",
      "Hank",
      "Saul"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Who said this line, 'Power is Power' ? Reference : Game of Thrones",
    answer: "Cersei Lannister",
    options: [
      "Rob Stark",
      "Cersei Lannister",
      "Daenerys",
      "Littlefinger"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which fruit, in the movie The Godfather appeared whenever a death was about to happen ?",
    answer: "Orange",
    options: [
      "Orange",
      "Apple",
      "Guava",
      "Peach"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which character in Twilight could percieve the future ?",
    answer: "Alice",
    options: [
      "Bella",
      "Rosalie",
      "Alice",
      "Jasper"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "In which British city is The Peaky Blinders set in ?",
    answer: "Birmingham",
    options: [
      "Manchester",
      "Oxford",
      "Newcastle",
      "Birmingham"
    ]
  },

];